[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
Bang!
[scoffs]
[♪ music fades]
Whoa.
You didn't even blink.
Huh? [gun clicks]
I saw you flinch.
I'm Jin Isoo, the owner of this place.
And I'm a violent crime detective.
[♪ tense pulsating music playing]
-Is this real?
-It's real.
A rich cop.
[Seongwook scoffs softly]
I really liked this place.
Now I won't be coming back.
Since you're here,
how about a game with me?
If you win, I'll give you
a lifetime membership for free.
But if I win,
you just need to answer my questions.
-Ever heard the word "whippersnapper"?
-No.
I've never heard such a dated word before.
[scoffs] That's what you are.
Look it up when you get home.
Hey, I guess you don't feel confident.
I heard you were
all washed up and retired.
How dare you, you asshole.
I'm talking with your boss here.
Stay out of this, lackey.
[♪ music swells]
Not feeling confident?
About winning against a whippersnapper?
[♪ music fades]
[Seongwook sighs]
The club's management rights.
If you want to bet with me,
make it worth my while.
Whoa, you sure drive a hard bargain.
Deal!
[♪ jaunty, dramatic music playing]
I'll shoot first.
Pull.
[gunshot]
-[gunshot]
-[target shatters]
[casings clatter]
Pull.
[gunshot]
So your eyes are still holding up.
What?
[gun clicks]
STYLE
::cue()
[Isoo] Pull.
[gunshot]
Pull.
[Seongwook] Pull.
[gunshot]
[Isoo] Pull.
Pull.
[gunshot]
[casing clatters]
[Seongwook] Pull.
[gunshot]
Pull.
[target whizzing]
[exhales sharply]
Looks like I won. Huh?
Age catches up with everyone.
[♪ music fades]
EPISODE 8
-[Isoo] Detective Joo.
-What happened?
-What's with the outfit?
-Never mind that.
Ham Seongwook says
he'll tell us everything.
What? How?
-[♪ jaunty music playing]
-[exhales smugly]
I made a bet with him over this club.
People like him can't resist a challenge.
You know it, too.
You made a bet with him over this club?
-Is this yours?
-I bought it yesterday.
The owner was deep in debt,
so he wanted to sell it quickly.
[exhales incredulously] How much was it?
Actually, never mind.
Why would I need to know?
[sighs] I almost missed one shot,
so that really had me sweating.
Because you'd lose the club?
No, because I would lose to him.
How could I live with myself
after losing to a washed-up thug?
That's true.
You can't lose to a washed-up thug.
Anyway, I got him to the table.
I did pretty well, right?
[chuckles] Yes, you did well.
You really are a cheat code.
[clicks tongue, sighs contentedly]
[♪ music fades]
I'm Joo Hyera from Gangha Police.
[Isoo] She's my team leader.
She'll be joining us. Have a seat.
[exhales deeply]
I lost, so I will keep my word.
Oh, like a real man.
Don't lie to us now.
I never lie.
On April 12th, Magician Park Jaeha
died during a performance.
We believe he was murdered.
Please tell us everything that happened
between you and Mr. Park Jaeha.
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
There's an expression
about being the apple of one's eye.
Only someone who's had a child
can understand what that feels like.
My daughter
is the apple of my eye.
When she was little,
my wife died from an illness.
I cherished her,
treasured her,
and raised her with the utmost care.
But not long ago,
she said she got a boyfriend.
So I put my boys on him
to find out what kind of guy he was.
[♪ music turns ominous]
But it turns out...
STYLE
::cue()
Seven women?
[inhales sharply, exhales]
Yes.
[scoffs]
And my Sujeong is...
[in English] "Honey 7"?
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[in Korean] Bring that bastard to me.
PARK JAEHA'S MAGIC FIRE
[whistling]
[in English] "Park Jaeha's Magic Fire."
-[chuckles smugly]
-[henchman whistles]
[whistles]
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
Park Jaeha?
Yes?
Come with us.
Who are you?
Wait, what is this about?
[exclaims, groans]
-Hey, magician.
-Yes?
Do you want us to beat you up
and drag you away,
or will you come quietly?
[breath trembling]
-I'll come quietly.
-Let's go.
[exclaims in pain]
[♪ music swells, stops]
Seriously, what's this about?
Just try saying one more word.
You'll definitely regret it.
I think you've misunderstood something--
[exclaims]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
Drive.
[tires screeching]
[♪ music swells]
[gasps]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
I'm Sujeong's father.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me just once.
Forgive you for what?
I'll break up with her right away,
and I won't ever see her again!
Which means
you never really loved her to begin with?
What?
You never cared about her,
but you dragged my daughter
in and out of hotels?
[exclaims]
I didn't do anything to her.
We only slept holding hands!
It's true!
I swear on my dead mother!
I promise! It's true!
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Which hand?
We promise with the right.
[yelps]
Wait!
What are you doing to me?
I used to be in the mob.
What?
Our mob always pays people back in kind.
Your hand touched my daughter,
so I'm going to take it.
No, you can't!
Don't do this to me!
Just beat me...
[grunts, groans]
Damn it, you hit me again.
Wait, hold on! Please, sir, wait!
Wait.
If I...
lose this hand,
Sujeong will be sad.
-Cut it off.
-[Jaeha] No!
Wait, hold on!
Please wait, sir. Please.
Wait.
[breathing heavily]
Please just let me...
do my last show. [sobbing]
This will be the end
of my life as a magician.
[continues sobbing]
No, sir, please.
STYLE
::cue()
-[♪ music fades]
-That's all.
My boys were just waiting there
to bring him to me after the show.
Would his fingers have been enough?
She's your cherished, treasured daughter.
[clicks tongue, inhales deeply]
[exhales] Hey...
I wasn't serious
about cutting his hand off.
I was just... [scoffs softly]
...threatening him
so he'd end things for good.
That bastard was truly
nothing but a spineless coward.
I'm done talking now.
I'll be on my way.
[Sujeong] Dad.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Oh, goodness.
My princess. This must've been heavy.
You said you were arriving late.
Hey, take this.
What's wrong?
Was it you?
What do you mean?
[breath trembles]
Hey.
[whispering] It's not loaded.
[sighs softly in relief]
Did you kill him?
I didn't.
[voice shaking] I told you I loved him.
Were you the one who killed him?
[breath trembling]
If you really think I killed him,
pull the trigger.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
I'll tell you everything
about the kind of man Park Jaeha was.
[♪ music fades]
Can we believe him?
He said he never lies.
Why would he mention
that he threatened to cut off his fingers?
He's confident because he didn't kill him.
Or the victim's dead,
so it doesn't matter if he tells us.
Besides, you have to mix in
a bit of truth when telling a lie.
So you think Ham Seongwook is the culprit?
[sighs thoughtfully]
No.
Ham Seongwook would've killed him quietly.
He'd never do it onstage.
That's true.
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
[inhales sharply] The culprit killed him
while countless people were watching.
That's the crux of this case.
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
Excuse me.
Oh. Yes, can I help you?
I'm with the police.
Oh, right.
This is you in this photo, isn't it?
Uh, yes, it's me.
Did you notice anything strange
on the day of the incident?
[scoffs softly] Anything strange?
Yes, anything out of the ordinary.
Uh...
[sharp inhale]
That day, I was quite worn out.
I don't know why.
I thought maybe it was because
I had a drink the night before,
but the equipment felt heavy.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-Heavy?
-Yes.
Did you see Mr. Park Jaehyung
at the workshop that day?
No, I didn't.
He usually comes out
to check the equipment,
but he wasn't there that day.
-Okay, thank you.
-Sure.
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
[sighs softly]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
ORAL MEDICATION
PARK JAEHYUNG
[♪ suspenseful, ticking music playing]
[pen clicks]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[sniffs]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-[jerry can thuds]
-[kerosene sloshing]
-Hello.
I'm Detective Choi Kyungjin
from Gangha Police.
Ah, right.
Did anyone buy kerosene
from here recently?
I think there were a few.
Could you check for me?
Of course.
[exhales softly]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
-[chuckles softly]
-[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
[Isoo] Mmm...
If Ham Seongwook isn't the killer...
Let's think this through
from the beginning. [sighs]
The three women
who have access to the equipment.
And also,
Park Jaehyung.
[Isoo sighs thoughtfully]
[Hyera sighs softly]
Where were you?
[sighs wearily]
I went to the theater.
Park Jaehyung wasn't
in the workshop that day.
Huh?
Then what happened?
He was there when we went.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Mr. Park Jaeha?
I'm Park Jaehyung.
Jaeha's brother.
The staff didn't see him.
And there was a heater in the workshop.
A kerosene heater.
The kerosene can was half empty.
I found out who bought the kerosene.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
No one bought kerosene
from gas stations near the theater,
so I checked the suspects' neighborhoods.
[keyboard key clacks]
That's Ms. Lee Jiyun.
I told you! I was right.
Lee Jiyun and Park Jaehyung
were working together.
[sighs smugly]
God, my instincts are unbelievable.
He might be right.
I found medication in his workshop.
I checked with the hospital.
He has terminal cancer.
No way.
[sighs softly]
On the verge of death,
he wanted to kill his brother,
whom he was jealous of?
[sighs deeply]
He must've felt so wronged, huh?
He's going to die anyway,
so why not take his brother with him?
And Ms. Lee Jiyun joined his plan
after being betrayed.
[Hyera] Park Jaehyung poured kerosene
into the equipment.
[in English] Okay.
[Hyera, in Korean] And Lee Jiyun
pretended not to know?
Find out where Lee Jiyun is.
Got it.
[♪ music fades]
DIRECTOR LEE JIYUN
-[sighs]
-[box snaps shut]
[knock at door]
-[Hyera] Ms. Lee Jiyun.
-Yes?
-[door closes]
-[Hyera] Can we have a word with you?
-Sure.
-[Isoo] Oh...
-It looks like you were packing.
-[Jiyun, softly] Mmm.
The show's over now.
I need to find another project.
[Isoo] Mmm...
So, what can I do for you?
Two days before the incident,
at Sankyeong Gas Station,
you bought kerosene, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Why?
-To kill the one who betrayed you?
-What?
[Isoo inhales sharply]
You gave your boyfriend of one year
money to get a place together,
only to find he had seven girlfriends.
You must've been furious.
I understand. Mmm.
What are you talking about?
We found kerosene inside the casket.
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ tense music playing]
You're the only one
who bought kerosene before the incident.
Jaehyung asked me to buy it for him.
The workshop gets cold,
so he uses a heater.
He can't go out in a wheelchair to buy it.
Mmm...
Is that all you did for him?
I have a feeling you did more.
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm already pissed off as it is.
You knew he was going to kill
his brother, didn't you?
You knew and looked the other way.
Or...
were you in on it from the start?
[Jiyun] Detective.
I'm not that dumb.
Of course, I'm angry.
It wasn't just another woman or two.
But I didn't know that
until after he died.
Even if I had known,
why would I ruin my life
over a bastard like that?
I'd get caught this quickly.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
If you're still that suspicious,
I'll do a polygraph, or whatever it takes.
I'll do it all!
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
NATIONAL FORENSIC SERVICE
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
[Dr. Yoon] I'll begin the autopsy.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[grunts softly]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
The older one had cancer,
the other was hunted by thugs.
Uh...
But why didn't he run away?
[Hyera] What?
Ham Seongwook was going to cut off
his fingers that day.
Why didn't he run away?
[sniffs]
[gasps softly] Detective Park.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells, fades]
[Isoo sighs softly]
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello, Dr. Yoon.
The victim didn't burn to death.
There's no soot in his trachea or bronchi.
Then...
[♪ tense, ticking music playing]
He was already dead before the fire.
-[line disconnects]
-What is it?
He was already dead before the fire.
[Kyungjin] Detective Joo!
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
[panting] It's the same size
as the casket.
And it smells of kerosene.
It wasn't Park Jaeha.
Park Jaehyung is the one who died.
[scoffs incredulously]
The one who had to disappear
was Park Jaeha.
So he vanishes in the middle of his act?
He kills Park Jaehyung
and puts him inside the casket.
[thuds]
[Isoo] Then he disappears
during the show...
[flames whooshing]
Making Park Jaeha the victim.
Because they're twins.
This is basically teleportation.
We just need his fingerprint.
Let's go.
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
[exhales softly]
Mr. Park Jaeha!
Mr. Park Jaehyung!
There you are.
What were you up to?
I have to clear this place out.
-Oh, that's a lot of work. Let me help.
-No, it's all right.
[♪ dramatic spy music playing]
I'm going to take my time.
[Isoo] You shouldn't push yourself
in your condition.
-Shall I pack this?
-Don't touch...
[in English] Magic.
Magic...
[in Korean] Did it disappear?
How did this...
Jin Isoo.
Stop bothering him and let's go.
Sorry to bother you.
Jeez.
Let us know if you need any help.
Anything, anytime. Detective Jin.
[Jaehyung, softly] Goodness.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Sir!
We need fingerprints.
[Kyungjin] It's urgent.
[♪ music fades]
[Hyera] He kept up the wheelchair act
even with no one around.
He's very meticulous.
We were really in sync just now.
[chuckles] Yeah,
your acting is pretty good.
[exhales smugly]
I'm just too talented for my own good.
[sighs heavily]
Anyway, I've never seen a case like this.
He killed his own brother to disappear.
Let's get him
the second we get his fingerprints.
I'll be the one to cuff him.
[chuckles softly] Sure.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
[tape ripping]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music fades]
-[cell phone vibrating]
-[Isoo sighs]
-[Junyoung] Detective Joo.
-Yes?
We didn't find any fingerprints.
Huh?
They say he would've suffered burns
while working with fire.
We'll see if there are any other ways.
Okay, got it.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
He was packing a passport earlier.
If he bolts, we'll never catch him.
[sighs in exasperation]
We need a clever way to...
[♪ bright musical sting]
There is a clever way.
[♪ jaunty, suspenseful music playing]
Like what?
Stay here and don't let him get away.
I'll make him shout out
that he's Park Jaeha.
Jin Isoo!
-[sighs softly]
-[♪ music fades]
Why did he suddenly call for us?
-You're all here!
-Hello.
What a relief.
-It's been a while.
-Yes, sir.
I have an urgent project.
What's the name
of that movie we're working on?
The End of Humanity.
Let's rehearse Scene 27.
Right now.
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
[tires screech]
ISCG INFECTION CONTROL
[♪ upbeat rock music continues]
STYLE
::cue()
PROJECT ISCG:
THE END OF HUMANITY
[♪ music fades]
[grunts softly]
[exhales softly]
[sighs deeply]
Time to say goodbye to this place.
[scoffs softly]
[Isoo] Mr. Park Jaehyung.
Mr. Park Jaehyung! Where are you?
Ah! Are you Park Jaehyung?
Yes, I am.
-[♪ quirky, dramatic music playing]
-[sprayers hissing]
[Isoo] Did you have blood tests done
at Munsan Hospital?
A deadly, contagious virus
was found in your blood.
What?
[Isoo] This is a virus
that's never been identified before.
If this gets out...
it's the end of humanity.
What?
[Kyungjin] It looks like
the virus is only in here!
It hasn't spread outside.
[Junyoung] We must kill the host
and burn this whole place down!
[Isoo] Let's take him to the lab.
[Kyungjin] What if more people
get infected?
Tens of thousands could die
before we have a vaccine!
[Junyoung mutters, grunts]
[gasps] Wait, hold on!
[Junyoung] We must kill him here!
[Isoo, sighs] Is this truly the only way?
[Kyungjin] If we keep quiet,
we can stop a catastrophe.
[Junyoung] I'll take responsibility.
[Isoo] Mr. Park Jaehyung.
We're sorry.
Your sacrifice will save humanity.
What?
[Isoo] You are our hero,
Mr. Park Jaehyung.
[Kyungjin, in English] Hero.
[Isoo, in Korean] We promise
to remember you.
Shoot him.
-[Junyoung grunts]
-Wait! Please, wait.
Wait.
I'm...
not Park Jaehyung.
[Isoo] Do not be afraid of death.
Shoot him.
-[Junyoung grunts]
-[Jaehyung] Wait, please!
Wait.
I'm...
not Park Jaehyung.
I'm Park Jaeha, his brother!
[Isoo] Mr. Park Jaeha died a few days ago.
-[Junyoung grunts]
-Wait, stop!
I'm...
I'm the magician, Park Jaeha!
-Look!
-[all exclaim in disbelief]
[Jaeha] Look.
My brother couldn't walk
after his accident, but look.
Park Jaeha's magic fire!
The waltz.
Look. See?
I'm light on my feet! See that?
-Right?
-[Isoo, in English] What the...
[in Korean] I'm Jaeha!
[Isoo, in English] Oh, my God.
[in Korean] Who?
Park Jaeha!
[Kyungjin] Wow.
[Isoo scoffs incredulously]
[in English] Jesus.
[in Korean] Park Jaeha.
Huh? Huh?
You said you're Park Jaeha, right?
[♪ upbeat swing jazz music playing]
Park Jaeha.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Park Jaehyung.
[handcuffs clicking]
[exhales heavily]
[sighs softly]
[exclaims smugly]
You're pretty startled
for a magician, huh?
[in English] Surprise!
That virus...
[in Korean] It's a trick.
A show just for Park Jaeha.
[yelps]
[whimpers, gasps]
[softly] What?
[exhales incredulously]
What on earth?
What's ISCG?
It's not part of the police, is it?
[Isoo] This?
ISOO COOL GUY
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
Tell us what happened.
Sujeong's dad
sent his men to take me to him.
[Seongwook] Your hand
is mine.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
Cut it off.
Wait.
Aren't you afraid?
The only thing I'm afraid of...
is not keeping my promise to the audience.
It's a shame. [sighs]
I'd hoped a man like you
would become my son-in-law.
That's not what we heard.
[sighs regretfully]
So I told him.
Once I finish my final performance,
I will come back here on my own. And then,
you can take my hand.
Did you really mean that?
-[♪ music fades]
-No. In all honesty,
I just couldn't do it.
How can a magician live without his hands?
Huh?
I spent all day thinking it over,
then I went to see my brother.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
Because I need money to run away.
Jaehyung.
[gasps softly]
ORAL MEDICATION
[breath trembles]
But
he was dead.
[♪ music swells, fades]
[Isoo] Hey.
If you lie, we'll know.
[frantically] I'm not lying.
It's the truth.
I promise. I even have his suicide note.
[exhales sharply] I promise.
Anyway... [breath trembling]
...I knew he had cancer,
but I didn't know it was that serious.
It seems there was no way to treat it.
So then what did you do?
At first...
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
...I was really shaken up...
[breathing heavily]
but then I thought,
"I really am lucky."
We're twins,
so it's the perfect way to disappear.
[chuckles]
Oh. So,
your brother died,
but you came up with that perfect plan?
[sighs]
He was already dead,
so I thought he was
helping me until the very end.
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
FAREWELL NOTE
DAILY LIFE WAS PAINFUL
THANK YOU ALL FOR EVERYTHING
[♪ music increases in tempo]
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ music slows, fades]
Jaeha.
Hey, Luna.
I had a really scary dream today.
What kind of dream?
A dream about you dying.
Ah.
Can't you skip today's show?
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
I have to treat it
like my last performance
and do my best.
[gunshot]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[fire roaring]
-[burning wood crashes]
-[Dahee screams]
[screaming in horror]
[audience exclaiming in horror]
Get everyone to safety first.
[clamoring]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[breathing heavily]
[knock at door]
[Isoo] Hello? This is the police.
[switch clicks]
[wheelchair whirs]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
So you burned your dead brother
to disappear completely?
Of course, I didn't feel good about it.
But he was going to be cremated anyway.
[sighs sarcastically]
[exhales] I'm so touched.
Is this what people call
the total package?
Love life, family, colleagues,
performance, character.
All completely trash.
Trash?
I've never met anyone so obnoxious before.
[breathing heavily]
[♪ quirky, dramatic music playing]
What else could I do?
I was scared.
Ever had your hand go into a straw cutter?
It's really sharp.
Anyway, all I did
was burn my brother's dead body,
so is there any chance
I could get a suspended sentence?
Isoo Cool Guy.
Uncross your fingers.
Suspended sentence, my ass.
You think the judges are
crazy enough to do that, huh?
What's the matter with you?
Aren't you being a bit harsh?
-Come here.
-[exclaims]
[♪ music fades]
Jaeha's alive?
Yes. Uh...
He used his dead brother
so he could run away.
Huh? That's so creepy.
Then the dream I had...
Mmm, it was about Park Jaehyung.
I guess you really can see the future.
[Jiyun sighs]
I can't believe the person I loved
was that messed up.
[sighs deeply] I know how you feel.
I always fall for the bad women.
-I wonder why.
-[Jiyun scoffs softly]
Actually, Waiter Hong!
Give us your most expensive whiskey.
No, a drink to celebrate.
STYLE
::cue()
Give us a bottle of champagne.
[Jiyun scoffs softly]
[♪ upbeat, jaunty music playing]
Now,
you're finally free
from that piece of trash,
so here's to your new life.
-[clinking]
-Cheers.
Mmm.
[sighs in exasperation]
I really don't think I'll feel any better
until I punch that bastard.
Mmm...
[in English] Good idea.
[in Korean] I like it.
Yes, cheers again.
[clinking]
[inhales sharply]
[exhales softly]
[♪ music fades]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
Park Jaeha? I heard he's dead.
What's a dead guy doing here?
-Show us.
-Show us a magic trick.
How can I do magic here?
Do it.
-Please stop.
-Do it.
[Jaeha] Don't touch me.
Oh, those guys are back again?
-Did you need something?
-Ah.
I need a word.
[♪ quirky, suspenseful music playing]
[whispering] We'll take
Park Jaeha out and...
[continues indistinctly]
Stop touching me.
Do some magic for us.
Mr. Park Jaeha,
you're being moved to jail. Come out.
[chuckles in relief]
-Show us before you go.
-Don't go.
Go left.
My God, you look terrible, Mr. Park.
Come here.
It's all right.
[in English] Now, follow me.
Oh! Oh...
[♪ music fades]
[chuckles nervously]
[in Korean] Did you come to say goodbye?
We couldn't just let you go.
-You son of a bitch.
-What?
[♪ quirky music playing]
-You!
-You bastard! How could you?
You shouldn't be doing this, ladies.
The stomach!
-[officer] That's enough.
-[Dahee] Get out of the way.
You bastard!
[Jaeha] I...
[Jiyun panting]
I loved all of you.
[exclaims]
Shut your mouth.
[Hyera] What's going on?
Right. Isn't the transport van over there?
I guess I was mistaken.
What? It's at the front gate.
It's the front gate. Ah, my mistake.
Mistake?
Yes, exactly. Nobody's perfect.
Hey, take him away.
[Jaeha] I really loved you.
-I mean it.
-Bro.
Well done. Time to go home.
You've got a mean punch.
Ever thought about boxing?
Jin Isoo.
-Submit a written apology.
-A written apology.
That's my specialty. You got it.
-[scoffs]
-[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
[sneezing]
[door opens]
[Jaeha sighs softly]
[♪ gentle, wistful music playing]
Sujeong.
[chuckles]
My Sujeong.
You look beautiful today.
Like a cherry blossom. [chuckling]
[sighs softly]
Did you come all the way here to see me?
Jaeha.
You'll be out of here soon.
My dad hired a great lawyer.
[exhales sharply]
[voice shaking] I don't know
what I'd do without you.
You were my first love.
But...
[inhales deeply, exhales]
...my life feels meaningless now.
[breath trembles]
I'll make it up to you.
From now on,
I'll be really good to you.
You should.
I'll be spending every day
waiting for you to get out.
[♪ music fades]
Once you're out,
I'm going to kill you myself.
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[chuckling nervously]
Why would you say
something so scary, Sujeong?
Try running if you want.
Wherever you hide,
I'm going to find you.
-[♪ music fades]
-What?
All the best until then.
[♪ quirky music playing]
Wait, Sujeong.
Sujeong!
Sujeong, wait!
You've suddenly changed!
Why are you doing this to me?
[voice shaking] If you do this too,
what am I supposed to do?
[sobbing]
[♪ music fades]
[line ringing over car speaker]
[automated voice] The number
you have dialed is unavailable.
Why isn't he picking up?
MR. CHOI
[line connects, ringing]
-Yes, Detective Jin.
-Hi, Mr. Kim.
I can't seem to reach the chairman lately.
Is he very busy?
He's on vacation.
-Vacation?
-He didn't say he was traveling.
-Shall I call him for you?
-No, it's fine.
He'll be reading books at home, then.
That's his idea of a vacation.
I'll go to his house.
[engine revving]
[doorbell chimes]
What on earth?
-[door unlocks]
-[digital lock beeps]
-[door closes]
-Mr. Choi, it's me!
[digital lock beeps]
Mr. Choi!
PRE AND POST STOMACH CANCER SURGERY
PRE-SURGERY PREPARATION
[♪ gentle, melancholy music playing]
ADMISSION INFORMATION
[sighs softly]
What are you doing here?
Detective Jin.
I asked, what are you doing?
How did you know I was here?
STYLE
::cue()
[Isoo sighs]
Were you never going to tell me?
It's not a serious illness.
And the surgery went well.
I thought of you as family.
But it looks like I meant nothing to you.
I just didn't want to bother you.
Did I scare you?
[sighs softly]
In my recent case,
a terminal cancer patient
took his own life.
But then I hear that you have cancer.
[sighs heavily]
I'm sorry.
[Isoo sighs softly]
[♪ music fades]
[Isoo sighs]
Why is your hospital room so shabby?
It's not shabby at all.
It's a perfectly nice room.
You don't even have any flowers.
I don't need flowers at my age. [chuckles]
And your clothes are all wet.
How are you going to get changed, huh?
As if you'd bother me.
Take it off and change.
I'll do it myself later.
[inhales sharply] Take it off.
You need to change!
Uh... [exhales]
[♪ gentle, poignant music playing]
[grunts softly]
GET WELL SOON
Thank you.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[sneezes]
Whoa!
-Looks like someone was here.
-[coughs]
Yes.
Someone I think of as a son stopped by.
[chuckles]
The scent's quite strong.
It is. [sneezes]
[chuckling]
[exhales sharply]
[panting]
[♪ music fades]
[cell phone vibrating]
Hey, babe.
[Kyungjin gasps]
[whispering] Shoot, I forgot.
Okay, I'll be right there. Sorry.
[line disconnects]
Hey, where are you going?
To see my girlfriend.
We're supposed to hang out today.
I forgot I had a date. Sorry, bro!
Hey!
[sighs]
He's completely whipped by his girlfriend.
-[sighs in exasperation]
-[cell phone vibrating]
Hi, Jiwon.
What? Where are you?
I'll be right there. I won't be long.
-[line disconnects]
-Hey, what's going on?
Jiwon hurt herself.
I need to go. Sorry. Bye.
Hey, you're...
[♪ quirky music playing]
He's the one who's whipped.
[exhales incredulously]
[clicks tongue]
[line connects, ringing]
-[line clicks]
-Hello? Yes, it's me.
I can't make it today,
so I'll have to cancel.
[line disconnects]
Where is everyone? I thought
you were having a guys-only party.
They betrayed me.
[keyboard clacking]
[♪ music fades]
Jiwon.
[panting] What happened?
Are you badly hurt?
No. [sighs]
I was trying to get back into running
and pulled something.
I think it might be broken.
[sighs heavily]
Let's go to the hospital. Hop on.
[chuckles] I'm joking. Honestly.
Sit here.
Are you sure you're okay?
[Dr. Yoon] Mmm.
[♪ gentle, tender music playing]
[both chuckle]
[clears throat] Right now...
[sighs] ...I just need some comforting.
[Dr. Yoon chuckles]
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
[Kyungjin] This looks gorgeous.
[♪ soft ambient music
playing in background]
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, leave this to me.
I didn't do anything for you on White Day.
You don't have to lift a finger today.
Here, open up.
Leave it. I'll eat it myself.
-I'm going to eat it.
-[scoffs]
Whoa!
It's delicious!
Mmm!
It's good, right? Wow!
Isoo's recommendations never disappoint.
Babe, you know
we caught Park Jaeha, right?
Do you know how we did it?
Sometimes I really think Isoo is a genius.
-[fork clatters on table]
-No, he is a genius.
We should break up.
What?
What did you just say?
I want to break up.
[♪ quirky, dramatic music playing]
You're breaking up with me over tonkatsu?
Don't you know why I want to break up?
I'm asking because I don't.
[scoffs] Forget it. What more
can I possibly say to you?
I'm leaving.
Excuse me. Can you
box up this tonkatsu for me?
Wow. You're getting it to go right now?
Hey, the tonkatsu did nothing wrong.
But still...
Thank you.
Uh...
Have a good life, with your beloved Isoo.
Bye.
Wow!
[scoffs]
[chuckling]
-It's still delicious.
-[♪ music fades]
[sighs wearily] Story of my life.
Stabbed in the back by guys.
Time to go home!
Want to get a drink with me?
-[Isoo] Cheers.
-[clink]
[♪ soft jazz music playing in background]
[slurps]
[exhales contentedly]
How's the aroma, huh? Amazing, isn't it?
[sniffs]
Yeah, it's amazing.
[sighs smugly] I spent eight whole months
trying everything to nail this flavor.
[exhales incredulously]
I drink soju and beer,
so I can't really tell.
Oh, you've got no taste.
Want to try something new?
You can try whiskey starting today.
No, I'm good. [chuckles]
[Hyera inhales sharply]
You even know how to make whiskey.
You're full of surprises, Jin Isoo.
What's the matter with you?
Did another soul fall for my charms? Huh?
[scoffs, chuckles]
That said,
as a cop, you're undeniably
walking a fine line.
You'll fall if you're not careful.
Don't worry.
I was born in the Year of the Monkey.
I'm good at keeping balance.
[chuckles]
You just need to use me.
I'll do anything you need.
As the cheat code to solving cases.
Right, cheat code.
[clink]
[Isoo exhales softly]
Will you return to Hansu Group one day?
Mmm... The truth is...
[inhales deeply]
...I dumped it all on Mr. Choi
and ran away.
He's like an uncle and a father to me,
but now I'm worried
I put too much on his shoulders.
[Isoo] Hmm.
By the way,
why did you return to Gangha?
It's odd. You were
doing great at Counterterrorism.
I have someone I need to catch.
Who?
Tell me, we can catch them together.
STYLE
::cue()
Yu Seongwon.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Yu Seongwon?
The Yu Seongwon I know?
Yes.
What did he do?
Serial killings.
Where is Seongwon?
At his studio.
Let's go.
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
Chairwoman.
What brings you all the way here?
When are you leaving?
Uh...
I'm not sure.
I have another exhibition coming up.
Cancel it and leave.
That's going to be a problem.
You see, I can't return to the UK.
Wow!
That's a great expression.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Makes me want to sculpt it.
Wherever it is...
just pack up and leave quickly.
Why?
Do you find it unbearable
that I'm so much like you, Mom?
[♪ music resumes tempo]
You know it's true.
You killed Dad.
And I...
uh, wonder...
[sings] who I killed.
[chuckles]
You want to lock me up
in a psych ward again, don't you?
Because I'm your Achilles' heel.
But...
that's not going to happen.
Your son is famous now.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Leaving so soon?
Not even a hug
after being apart for four years?
Are you scared of me?
-And you call yourself a mother?
-[♪ music swells]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
Keep an eye on him
so he doesn't cause any trouble.
Yes, ma'am.
Call me if anything happens.
[♪ tense, pulsating music playing]
Mr. Hwang.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, understood, ma'am.
[car engine starts]
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ gentle piano music
playing in background]
She's beautiful.
[chuckles softly]
[bartender] Who is she?
Someone who's obsessed with me.
[chuckles softly]
Is she a stalker?
You could say that.
I'm wondering if I should make her
the model for my next sculpture.
You're the sculptor, Yu Seongwon, right?
I went to your exhibition.
How was it?
Uh...
When I was looking at your pieces,
I almost felt like I couldn't breathe.
[chuckles softly]
I felt overwhelmed, I guess.
[chuckles] You flatter me.
It felt like there was
some hidden meaning behind it.
It's all out in the open,
but not quite revealing the truth.
You're very perceptive.
I used to study art.
I'm taking a break to work.
Why did you take a break?
Let's just say, no comment.
[Hyera] Four years ago,
two of Yu Seongwon's models disappeared.
And one of his underclassmen.
They were all closed
as missing persons cases,
but I think Yu Seongwon killed them.
[♪ ominous music playing]
What do you think?
Is the Yu Seongwon you know
capable of killing people?
No, the Seongwon I know
is timid and soft-hearted.
Do you have any evidence?
No, just my gut feeling.
His alibi checked out.
[♪ melancholy piano music playing]
Then it might not be him.
I was contacted by the UK police recently.
Two of Yu Seongwon's models are missing.
I have to submit a piece
for a contemporary art exhibition,
but I can't seem to find a model.
Shall I introduce you to someone?
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
SONG AREUM
How about you, Areum?
STYLE
::cue()
Would you
be my model?
[♪ music swells]
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 8
THE TRUTH ABOUT YU SEONGWON COMES TO LIGHT
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
Special Cast. Son Woohyeon
Special Cast. Jung Chaeyeon
Special Cast. Heo Sungtae
-[all scream]
-[Hyera] Who is the deceased student?
Murder? No student
at our school would do that.
Was Seyeon alone yesterday?
[student 1] The principal
supervised her personally.
-Moon Seyeon's death was a curse.
-A curse?
Wait, I'll buy you cream puffs!
We have to focus on the curse.
[student 2] It's from the Witch Shop.
-Who do you want to curse?
-The police.
Why would the police...
[Hyera] Someone hated Moon Seyeon.
-[student 3] A senior died last year.
-A ghost?
Stay back!
-[Kyungjin] The CCTVs?
-[man] They were down.
It makes no sense.
They're still at the school.
[both gasp]
Be careful. Someone's after you.
That's a secret.
[woman] I have a bad feeling about this.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
CONTACT ANALYSIS: YU SEONGWON
VICTIM 3: KIM HEEJUN
MISSING SINCE 16 SEP 2021
[cell phone vibrating]
[in English] Yes, this is Joo Hyera.
Yes, I requested the file.
Two people.
Are they missing?
Right.
I understand. Thank you.
[line disconnects]
[sighs wearily]
Translated by Hyesoo Lee